oh my god
oh my god tommy's been bad
[Music]
what are you waiting for you know what
you have to do god i
i can't do it you want you have to do it
forgive me tommy
[Music]
zombies are raccoons right
no it's just zombies
oh you just killed tommy
all right listen up sheriff's
department's close by we'll be safe
there okay
stay close i'll get you out of here
they didn't get us okay we're still
alive
all right keep it together yeah okay we
gotta make it to that sheriff station
oh my god
[Music]
we got to go through them stay together
keep moving
and don't get bit go
hey are you getting this yeah what is
up all right let's go
this is crazy
[Music]
what
ain't um some these are some racist
zombies why would you even
lock the door i mean the window's broken
and
oh oh hell no
no no no
oh um oh what is that they seriously
wouldn't let her eat us
hey guys isn't this great
these racist zombies are leaving us
alone come on we having a party
the beer is here
[Applause]
hey man this is your first time no man i
i've been doing zombie extra work on
this show
since day one first season man my first
time
was your first time on this show my
first time being extra
at all ever kind of nervous oh wow okay
man hey man
i'm sorry about you you'll be all right
man it's okay man it's not that hard man
you'll be all right
i'm me personally dude i'm looking for
that lunge bump though
what's what's a lunge bomb oh that's uh
like if you um you get featured
if you lunge at somebody and then you
get a bump in your pay and if you really
lucky man
they blow your head off that's straight
bank right there that's right
assistant director gather round jerry
hey jerry i had a thought man about the
first scene that y'all not now stan oh
steve it's steve okay okay
i'm gonna need somebody to lunge at the
fence ah
you think you can handle it yeah oh
yeah it's his first dado he's kind of
nervous man he's kind of nervous this is
his first date okay so the director's
gonna yell action
mac's gonna come by and then you're just
gonna lunge into the fence like
you you want me to say grah oh say
whatever it's crazy
okay all right cool man hey you know hey
that's cool hey you know i got a lot
more experience man you can just use me
i've been here
day one first season so and okay cool
all right that's fine you're gonna go
with him
all right good for you man good for you
guys no don't do
you don't have to say god do whatever
hell you want to do man that's the
lunchbox that is the lunge bump man
you got it you got it on your first day
ever
being an extra ever you got it man good
for you
and action
what the hell was that cut oh man i
would be more than happy to fill in man
i'd be more than happy to step
in mac just remember when you're coming
through the factory that hey like your
mind is still in the car
i mean you all got to pick people based
on qualifications man you can't just be
picking random there's a good note
good note but maybe what i was doing
sort of superseded that
agreed yeah we were just discussing that
absolutely it supersedes it yeah but uh
let's do one that just
seeds it okay just same level we're
going again straight away okay right
away okay
reset okay he's not doing a good job at
it you're doing great though man
opportunity knocks you gonna answer the
door man
action
[Music]
i'll be more than happy to step in at
any time you want me to
i'd be more than happy to do it just a
certain sense of urgency is all we're
looking for
clock's ticking you got survivors to
find right can't tell you off something
real segment
this dude right here is not doing what a
zombie does this dude was literally on
our last take
waving his hand up in the air like this
jerry making beaker sounds he sound like
beaker from the muppets y'all thank you
that's great just a ticking clock on
this is all we're looking for because
there are survivors that's what we're
after okay
i found the ambivalence in there the
ambivalence is
art it's gorgeous and we love it but
there are zombies so if we could just
pick up the pace just a hair that'd be
great well straight away please right
away
jerry we're not doing night of the
living muppets are we we're not cause
the beaker is not a zombie do you have
any notes
yeah don't be a beaker quiet please
action
he actually just said the word zombie
come on
man you ever hear a zombie say the word
zombie before no you haven't i don't
think so
you know what get rid of this guy thank
you that's what i'm talking about y'all
i'm sorry dog but you're terrible at
this man
do your thing hey man no he talking
about him no he's talking about him
cause he said zombie thank you steve
no you want me to leave hey man i've
been up here staggering around here for
three and a half years
and i've been startling extras left and
right when do i get the start of the
lead huh one more for safety straight
away you're ready
action
hey what do we do if we have to go to
the bathroom
we like it i love it genius moving on i
got it